http://www.ccmgatx.org/privacy-policy/

Skip to the content
Privacy Policy
The Collin County Master Gardeners Association (CCMGA) is highly sensitive to your privacy interests and we believe we have a responsibility to protect your personal information.
In acknowledgment of its obligations, CCMGA has adopted the following Privacy Policy applicable to information about consumers that it acquires in the course of its business:
Acquisition of Information. We do not acquire any more information about consumers than is required by law or is otherwise necessary to provide a high level of service efficiently and securely.
Our Members and Privacy. We give access to personal information only to those members who require it to provide volunteer services as requested by the community.
Security Measures. Access to privacy-sensitive information is subject to rigorous procedural and technological controls, consistent with legal requirements and the demands of customer service.
Disclosure to Third Parties. We do not share your personal information with third parties.
If you have questions about this privacy policy, please send an e-mail to secretary@ccmgatx.org.
Gardening Advice
Let us help you with your gardening challenges or questions.
Ask a Master Gardener
Collin County Master Gardeners Association
Have a question about program or event?
Contact Us
Join our Email List
Stay informed about upcoming events and timely garden topics.
Add Me
Cookie Notice
Find out more about how this website uses cookies to enhance your browsing experience.
Accept Cookies
